YUKTI VERMA

Cyber Security Enthusiast | ISC2 CC Certified

Ludhiana, Punjab | yuktiverma01@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

CAREER SUMMARY:

A third year Computer Science and Engineering student, with a strong inclination towards cyber security and digital forensics, with 3+ months of experience in Ethical Hacking and CHFI. Certified in Cyber Security by ISC2. A ranked NCC cadet and Ex-Secretary: GU Student Council.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Craw Security, Saket, New Delhi

Ethical Hacking Trainee | July, 2023 - August 2023

- Completed comprehensive training in ethical hacking methodologies, tools, and techniques.
- Hands-on experience with popular hacking tools like Metasploit, Nmap, Wireshark, and Burp Suite, and strong understanding of network protocols and cryptography.

Craw Security, Saket, New Delhi

CHFI Trainee and Intern | June, 2023 - July, 2023

- Familiarity with forensic procedures for collecting, preserving, and presenting evidence.
- Trained in forensic imaging techniques for forensic analysis while maintaining chain of custody and data integrity.
- Familiarity with tools such as FTK (Forensic Toolkit) and Sleuth Kit for data acquisition, analysis, and reporting.

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

PScan: GUI Based Port Scanner

• Summer Internship Project | Built using Python | 2023

WebWarden: GUI Based website blocking Tool

GUI based | Built using Python | 2023

SQLiWatchdog: Web-Logs Scanner for SQL Injection Detection

CLI Based | RegEx based tool | Built using Python | 2024

EDUCATION:

2021 - Present | GNA University, Phagwara

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering

SKILLS:

- Programming languages: Python, Java
- Digital Forensics & Incident Response
- Tools: Wireshark, TcpDump etc.
- MySQL, Linux
- Basic Web Dev: HTML, CSS, JS
- Steganography, Cryptography

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Certified in Cyber Security(CC) by ISC2.
- RedHat System Administrator-I (RH-124)
- RedHat System Administrator-II (RH-134)
- Palo Alto: Fundamentals of Network Security.
- Wireshark Essentials Training